In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to learn how to pronounce the UH as in PUSH vowel.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音类似于PUSH中的UH元音。
To make this sound, the corners of the lips come in a little so the lips flare away from the face.
要发出这个音，嘴唇的两角稍微收拢，使嘴唇从脸部向外张开。
UH.
UH。
The back of the tongue lifts towards the back of the roof of the mouth.
舌头的后部抬起，靠近口腔顶部的后部。
The front of the tongue remains down, but it might be pulled slightly back so it's not quite touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
舌头的前部保持向下，但可能会稍微向后拉，以至于不完全接触下前牙的后部。
Let's look at this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个音。
The lips flare and the tongue inside the mouth is a little darker than on other vowels because the tongue is pulled back.
嘴唇张开，口腔内的舌头比其他元音稍微暗一些，因为舌头向后拉。
Here's the word TOOK.
这是单词TOOK。
The corners of the mouth come in to flare the lips.
嘴角收拢以张开嘴唇。
The back of the tongue lifts, and the front pulls back a little.
舌头的后部抬起，前部稍微向后拉。
In a stressed syllable, the vowel curves up, then down.
在重读音节中，元音先上升，然后下降。
TOOK.
TOOK。
UH.
UH。
In an unstressed syllable, it's lower and flatter in pitch, as well as quieter and quicker.
在非重读音节中，音调更低更平，声音也更轻更快。
The vowel is unstressed in the word GOODBYE.
在单词GOODBYE中，元音是非重读的。
UH.
UH。
Let's look at this word up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个单词。
Again, the lips flare and the tongue lifts in the back, pulling back the front of the tongue.
再次，嘴唇张开，舌头在后部抬起，前部向后拉。
Let's compare the stressed version on top with the unstressed version on the bottom.
让我们比较一下上面的重读版本和下面的非重读版本。
Notice the lips flare a little less for the unstressed vowel, hiding the bottom teeth.
注意非重读元音时嘴唇张开得稍微少一些，遮住了下牙。
Generally, the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong is more relaxed, and doesn't take the full mouth position.
通常，元音或双元音的非重读版本更放松，不需要完全的口腔位置。
In this case, a little less lip flare, and possibly less jaw drop.
在这种情况下，嘴唇张开得少一些，可能下巴也不需要张开太多。
This is because unstressed syllables are shorter, so we don't take the time to make the full mouth position.
这是因为非重读音节更短，所以我们不会花时间去做完整的口腔位置。
UH.
UH。
Unstressed, goodbye.
非重读，goodbye。
UH.
UH。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
UH.
UH。
Book.
Book。
Firewood.
Firewood。
UH.
UH。
Firewood.
Firewood。
Sugar.
Sugar。
UH.
UH。
Sugar.
Sugar。
Childhood.
Childhood。
UH.
UH。
Childhood.
Childhood。
Woman.
Woman。
UH.
UH。
Woman.
Woman。